Guide to the Housing and Feeding the Homeless Program, 1981-2000
Housing and Feeding the Homeless Program, 1981-2000
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Housing and Feeding the Homeless Program, 1981-2000
28-1-3161
6.6 cubic ft.
Correspondence, publications, newspaper clippings, scrapbooks.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, publications, newspaper clippings, scrapbooks and related records pertaining to the Housing and Feeding the Homeless Program that existed in the School of Hotel Administration at Cornell.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, publications, newspaper clippings, scrapbooks and related records pertaining to the Housing and Feeding the Homeless Program that existed in the School of Hotel Administration at Cornell.
SUBJECTS
Subjects:
Cornell University--Societies, etc.; Cornell University--Students.; Cornell University. School of Hotel Administration.; Hotel management schools--New York (State)--Ithaca.; Homelessness--United States.; Poor--United States.; Hunger--United States.; Food relief--United States.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Correspondence, Articles, Reports
Series II. Locations
Series III. Publications
Series IV. Miscellaneous
Series V. Videos
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Correspondence, Articles, Reports
  - President's Initiative Program Proposal and President Rhodes Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Homeless Program Summary with Appendices, 1987-1992 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Impact Study Letters of Support (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Atlantic Foundation Funding (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Homeless Course Guest Speakers (#1), 1988-1994 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Homeless Course Guest Speakers (#2), 1988-1994 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Various Guest Speaker Notes (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Course Syllabi: Housing and Feeding the Homeless Course, 1988-1994 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Hotel School Funding Issues: Homeless Program (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Other Funding Proposals: Homeless Program (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Hilton Funding: Homeless Program (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Homeless Program, 1988-1991 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Homeless Program, 1992-1994 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Homeless Program Miscellaneous Summaries (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Homeless Program News Articles (#1) (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Homeless Program News Articles (#2) (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Homeless Program Faculty Presentation (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Guest Speakers, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Homeless Program Summary, 1987-1991 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Homeless Program Correspondence (Miscellaneous) (#1) (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Homeless Program Correspondence (Miscellaneous) (#2) (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Homeless Program Correspondence (Miscellaneous) (#3) (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Articles on Homelessness Used in Homeless Course (#1) (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Articles on Homelessness Used in Homeless Course (#2) (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Articles on Homelessness Used in Homeless Course (#3) (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Articles on Homelessness Used in Homeless Course (#4) (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Key Reports on Public-Private Sector Programs to Address Homelessness CHRIE (The Council on Hotel, Restaurant and Institutional Education) Task Force for Battered Women Second Harvest: National Food Bank Network H.E.L.P. A Decent Place to Live: The Report of the National Housing Task Force (Advance Copy), March 1988 The D.C. Central Kitchen and Cornell University Food-Service Training Manual Student Handbook, 1993 Public/Private Housing Partnerships; the Urban Land Institute, 1990 New Partnerships - Building for the Future; Proceedings of the Canadian Conference to Observe the International Year of Shelter for the Homeless; Ottawa, Canada, September 13-16, 1987 100th Congress 2d Session, House of Representatives: FRANK305 Bill The Equity Trust Fund: Information for Prospective Participants, February 1994 NAHRO - The National Association of Housing and Redevelopment Officials Pulling Together: A Planning and Development Consensus-Building Manual; Urban Land Institute, 1994 HBO/Comic Relief (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Series II. Locations
  - Denver - The Samaritan House (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Connecticut - Urban Initiatives (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Phoenix, AZ - Casa Teresa Residence for Women (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Los Angles, CA - Shelter Partnership (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - San Diego, CA - St. Vincent de Paul Center (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - San Francisco, CA - American Friends Service (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Venice, CA - St. Joseph's (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Washington, DC (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Washington, DC - MANNA Housing for People (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Orlando, FL (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Atlanta, GA - Homelessness and the 1996 Olympics (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Honolulu, HI - Homeless Hawaii (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Chicago, IL - Homeless on the Move for Equality Inner City Development (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Massachusetts Housing Model (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Minneapolis-St. Paul, MN (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - St. Louis, MO (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - PRATT Bibliography and The Search for Shelter (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - New York, NY - PRATT (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - New York, NY - Transitional Housing (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Enterprise Foundation - James Rouse (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Syracuse, NY Housing (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Buffalo, NY - Coalition for the Homeless (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - New York, NY - The Hope Program (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - New York, NY - City Harvest (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - New York, NY - Holy Apostles' Soup Kitchen and The Covenant House (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - New York, NY - Local Initiatives Support Corporation (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Columbus, OH (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Youngstown, OH (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Portland, OR (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Philadelphia, PA (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Pittsburgh, PA (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Texas - Star of Hope (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Park City, UT (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Richmond, VA - SRO Housing (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Burlington, VT - Community Land Trust (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Seattle, WA - Homelessness (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - International Homelessness (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - London, England (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Mitch Snyder's Speech, Cornell Univ. Hotel School, 11/30/88 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Mitch Snyder Cornell Univ. Hotel School Class Presentation, 12/1/1988 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Community for Creative Non-Violence (CCNV) (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Community for Creative Non-Violence (CCNV) Consultation, Summer 1991 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Mitch Snyder News Releases (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Mitch Snyder Vita (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Single Room Occupancy (S.R.O.) Housing Corporation (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Los Angeles, CA - Weingart Center (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Ithaca, NY - Open Arms Health Center (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Series III. Publications
  - Hatkoff, Amy, and Karen Kelly Klopp. How to Save the Children. New York: Simon and Schuster, 1992. (Box 4)
  - Simon, Arthur. Bread for the World. New York: Paulist Press, 1975. (Box 4)
  - McGeady, Mary Rose. "God Isn't Done with Me Yet...": Letters from the Street. New York: Covenant House, 1993. (Box 4)
  - McGeady, Mary Rose. God's Lost Children: Letters from Covenant House. New York: Covenant House, 1991. (Box 4)
  - Bingham, Richard D., et al, ed. The Homeless in Contemporary Society. Newbury Park, Calif.: Sage Publications, 1987. (Box 4)
  - Kotlowitz, Alex. There Are No Children Here. New York: Anchor Books, 1991. (Box 4)
  - Erickson, Jon, and Charles Wilhelm, ed. Housing the Homeless. New Brunswick, NJ: Center for Urban Policy Research, 1986. (Box 4)
  - Walsh, Mary E. "Moving to Nowhere": Children's Stories of Homelessness. New York: Auburn House, 1992. (Box 4)
  - Popcorn, Faith. The Popcorn Report. New York: Doubleday Currency, 1991. (Box 4)
  - Hartman, Chester, et al. Displacement: How to Fight It. Berkeley, Calif.: National Housing Law Project, 1982. (Box 4)
  - Colman, Penny, ed. Hunger: Report and Recommendations of the New Jersey Commission on Hunger. Trenton, NJ: The New Jersey Commission on Hunger, 1986. (Box 4)
  - I. France, Research Associates. Contract Aftercare Project (CAP) Stage One Evaluation: Preliminary Report Prepared for the City of Toronto. March, 1987. (Box 4)
  - United States. Department of Housing and Urban Development. Office of Policy Development and Research. Housing Special Populations: A Resource Guide. HUD-1129-PDR. December, 1987. (Box 4)
  - Canada. Mortgage and Housing Corporation. Housing for Elderly People: Design Guidelines. NH 18-2/2-1987. 1987. (Box 4)
  - Canada. Mortgage and Housing Corporation. Housing Disabled Persons. NH21-8/1982E. 1982. (Box 4)
  - City of New York. Human Resources Administration. Bureau of Management Systems, Planning, Research and Evaluation. Family and Adult Services. Chronic and Situational Dependency: Long-Term Residents in a Shelter for Men. By Stephen Crystal, Mervyn Goldstein, and Rosanne Levitt. May, 1982. (Box 4)
  - City and County of San Francisco. Beyond Shelter: A Homeless Plan for San Francisco: Statement of Need. Presented by Art Agnos, Mayor. November, 1990. (Box 4)
  - Coalition for the Homeless. Reference Manual for Food, Shelter and Resources for the Homeless. November, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Bach, Victor, and Renee Steinhagen. Alternatives to the Welfare Hotel: Using Emergency Assistance to Provide Decent Transitional Shelter for Homeless Families. New York: Community Service Society, 1987. (Box 4)
  - Canada. City of Toronto. Alternative Housing Subcommittee of the Neighbourhoods Committee. A Case Study of Cityhome's Low Income Singles. (Box 4)
  - Santucci, Robert M., et al. Cost Cuts Manual: Nailing Down Savings for Least-Cost Housing. Columbia, MD: Enterprise Foundation, Rehab Work Group, 1987. (Box 4)
  - Blackburn, Anthony J. Single Room Occupancy in New York City. New York: Department of Housing Preservation and Development, 1986. (Box 4)
  - New York City. Human Resources Administration. New York City Five Year Plan for Housing and Assisting Homeless Adults. October, 1991. (Box 4)
  - Hopper, Kim, and Jill Hamberg. The Making of America's Homeless: From Skid Row to New Poor, 1945-1984. New York: Community Service Society of New York, December, 1984. (Box 4)
  - A Guide to Volunteer Opportunities in Tompkins County. Ithaca, N.Y.: Human Services Coalition and Information and Referral Service, 1993. (Box 4)
  - John Ellis and Associates, Architects. The Partnership Cost Study of Affordable Housing Projects. New York: The New York City Partnership, June, 1988. (Box 4)
  - Martin, William B. Managing Quality Customer Service: A Practicle Guide for Establishing a Service Operation. Los Altos, Calif.: Crisp Publications, Inc., 1989. (Box 4)
  - The New Homeless: Women, Children and Families: An Issues Forum on the Homeless. New York: Association of Junior Leagues, 1988. (Box 4)
  - Family and Child Homelessness. Washington, D.C.: Homelessness Information Exchange, September, 1988. (Box 4)
  - Greer, Nora Richter. The Search for Shelter. Washington, D.C.: The American Institute of Architects, 1986. (Box 4)
  - New York State. Division of Housing and Community Renewal. Housing Programs of New York State. Bronx, N.Y. (Box 4)
  - Evaluation of the Implementation of Grants to Provide Health Services to the Homeless (Draft Final Report). Center for Health Policy Studies, January 30, 1989. (Box 4)
  - White, Akua-Saah. Nutrition and Quantity Food Service Manual: A Guide for Volunteers and Staff/Working in Soup Kitchens and Food Pantries. New York: Cornell Cooperative Extension, August 1986. (Box 4)
  - Clipping Scrapbook (Box 4)
  - United States. Department of Health and Human Services. Helping the Homeless: A Resource Guide. Washington, D.C.: U.S. Dept. of Health and Human Services, Summer 1984 (Box 5)
  - Aaron, Kris. You Can Help the Homeless!: Here's How. Madison, W.I.: Wisconsin Builders Association, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Kneerim, Jill, ed. Homelessness: Critical Issues for Policy and Practice. Boston, M.A.: Boston Foundation, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Kelly, Gayle Leitch, Barbara S. Rauschenbach, and Cathy C. Campbell. Private Food Assistance in New York State: Challenges for the 1990s. Ithaca, N.Y.: Division of Nutritional Sciences, Cornell University, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Plain Talk About Emergency Food Centers: How to Start, Build, and Maintain a Center. Baltimore, MD: Maryland Food Committee, Inc., 1983 (Box 5)
  - Operation Food Search Incorporated. 6th Annual Report 1987. St. Louis, MO: Operation Food Search Incorporated, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Operation Food Search Incorporated. A Rapid Dispatch Food Distribution System. St. Louis, MO: Operation Food Search Incorporated, 1985 (Box 5)
  - Canada. Mortgage and Housing Corporation. A Consultation Paper on Housing Renovation. 1987? (Box 5)
  - Canada. Mortgage and Housing Corporation. Facilitating Production of Affordable Housing Through Regulatory Reform and Streamlining Approval Process. 1986 (Box 5)
  - Canada. Mortgage and Housing Corporation. Specific Disabilities and Home Modifications for Independent Living: A Guide for the Delivery of RRAP for Disabled Persons. 1987 (Box 5)
  - United States. Department of Housing and Urban Development. Homeless Assistance 1987-88. Washington, D.C.: U.S. Dept. of Housing and Urban Development, September 29, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Canada. Mortgage and Housing Corporation. Homelessness: A Bibliography. Ottawa, Ont.: Mortgage and Housing Corporation, July 1987 (Box 5)
  - Canada. Canadian Housing. Fall 1987 (vol. 4, no. 3) (Box 5)
  - New York State. Division of Housing and Community Renewal. Special Needs Housing Demonstration Program Annual Report 1985 (Box 5)
  - Dehavenon, Anna Lou. Toward a Policy for the Amelioration and Prevention of Family Homelessness and Dissolution: New York City's After-Hours Emergency Assistance Units in 1986-87. New York: The East Harlem Interfaith Welfare Committee, May 13, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Dehavenon, Anna Lou. The Tyranny of Indifference and the Re-Institutionalization of Hunger, Homelessness and Poor Health: A Study of the Causes and Conditions of the Food Emergencies in 1, 708 Households with Children in Manhattan, Brooklyn and the Bronx in 1986. New York: The East Harlem Interfaith Welfare Committee, July 15, 1987 (Box 5)
  - SRO Housing Corporation. Annual Report 1985-1986. (Box 5)
  - United Nations. UNESCO. 1987 International Year of Shelter for the Homeless. (Box 5)
  - Commonwealth of Massachusetts. Massachusetts Housing Partnership. A Guide to the Massachusetts Housing Partnership. Boston, MA. (Box 5)
  - Handwritten Title: "Kitchen Equipment Operational Manual". Work cited from Food Preparation for Hotels, Restaurants, and Cafeterias by Robert G. Haines, ATS 1960 (Box 5)
  - Habitat for Humanity. Fact Sheet. Newmarket, Ont. (Box 5)
  - The Homeless Times. Fall 1987, vol. 2, iss. 4. (Box 5)
  - Under One Roof. (Daily Newsletter of the Canadian Conference to Observe International Year of Shelter for the Homeless.) September 16, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Under One Roof. (Daily Newsletter of the Canadian Conference to Observe International Year of Shelter for the Homeless.) no date. (Box 5)
  - Joint issue: the circuit and Tenants' Bulletin. Sept. 1987, vol. 9, no. 2. (Box 5)
  - Shelter News. (Canadian Action for the International Year of Shelter for the Homeless.) August 1987, no. 3. (Box 5)
  - Insight on the news. June 27, 1988 (Box 5)
  - Mitchell, Yvette, ed. The Hunger Handbook 4th ed. Chicago, Ill.: Food Justice Programs, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Larsen, Amanda. The D.C. Central Kitchen and Cornell University Food-Service Training Manual (Trainer's Guidebook). Ithaca, N.Y.: Cornell University, 1993 (Box 5)
  - Larsen, Amanda. The D.C. Central Kitchen and Cornell University Food-Service Training Manual (Student Handbook). Ithaca, N.Y.: Cornell University, 1993. (Box 5)
  - United States. Department of Health and Human Services. Training Guide for Foodservice Personnel in Programs for Young Children. (Box 5)
  - Burnside Consortium. SRO Housing Management Handbook. Portland, O.R.: Burnside Consortium, 1983. (Box 5)
  - Hopper, Kim, Ellen Baxter, and Stuart Cox. Not Making It Crazy: Some Remarks on the Young Homeless Patient in New York City. New York, N.Y.: Community Service Society, November 2, 1981 (Box 5)
  - Reading Packet: Housing and Feeding the Homeless, HA 490/HSS 476, Fall 1992 (Box 5)
  - Reading Packet: Housing and Feeding the Homeless, HA 490/HSS 476, Fall 1993 (Box 5)
- Series IV. Miscellaneous
  - Hunger Table of Contents: Governor Cuomo's Message to the Legislature, January 1984 Policy, Advocacy, and Justice-The Case of the Food Assistance Reform by Janet Poppendieck (unpublished) Hunger, USA. Beacon Press, Boston, 1968 Public and Private Efforts to Feed America's Poor, GAO Report, June 1983 Report to the Presidents Task Force on Food Assistance (Executive Summary) January 1984 Hunger Watch-New York State (Part 1) February 1984 American Hunger Crisis, Harvard University 1984 Emergency Food Assisatnce Program (Federal Register 4/83) U.S. Conference of Mayors-Status Report: Emergency Food, Shelter and Energy Programs in 20 Cities (Box 6)
  - Homeless Table of Contents: Governor Cuomo's Message to the Legislature, January 1984 Editorial-Robert Maroney. The Urban and Social Review. Vol. 17 No. 1 Winter 1984 1933/1983 Never Again: Report of the National Governors Conference Homeless in America (Newsweek) The Homeless of New York (Public Interest) The Plight of Homeless Women, Madeline R. Stoner (Social Service Review) An Analysis of Public and Private Sector Provisions for Homeless People, by Madeline Stoner (The Urban and Social Change Review) Homelessness: A Comprehensive Policy Approach by Nancy K. Kaufman (The Urban and Social Change Review) Legal and Welfare Rights Advocacy: Complimentary Approaches in Organizing on Behalf of the Homeless by Michael Fabricant and Irwin Epstein (The Urban and Social Change Review) The Single Room Occupant Elderly (SRO), Rubenstein, unpublished (Box 6)
  - Notebook: Correspondence and literature about various United States hunger and food assistance programs. (Organized by geographical region.) (Box 6)
  - Philabundance/Philadelphia Committee for the Homeless (Box 6)
  - Homeless Shelters in New York State (Addresses) (Box 6)
  - Miscellaneous Media Coverage (including the Cornell University Housing and Feeding the Homeless Program) (Box 6)
- Series V. Videos
  - 60 Minutes- Brown vs. Koch (Homeless), Jan 24, 1988; V-1312 (Box 7)
  - 60 Minutes- Mitch Snyder Legacy, Dec 12, 1993; V-1343 (Box 7)
  - Build Homes not Bombs, V-1340 (Box 7)
  - CNN Endless Loop (2 copies), V-1341, V-1342 (Box 7)
  - Community Development Lending Making a Difference CRA, V-1301 (Box 7)
  - D.C. Central Kitchen- Food Service Job Training Program (Class of October 1999); ABC News- Nightline: Second Helpings (Broadcast November 26, 1999), 1999; V-1336 (Box 7)
  - D.C. Central Kitchen on Nightline, Thanksgiving Day, Nov 25, 1999; V-1314 (Box 7)
  - Donahue Homelessness, Joyce Brown, Jan 28, 1988; V-1303 (Box 7)
  - Egger, Robert- DC Central Kitchen, Apr 2, 1996; V-1319 (Box 7)
  - Ferry, Joseph- Bethesda Project, Apr 16, 1996; V-1306 (Box 7)
  - First Place School in Seattle (Homeless Children) 7 minutes; One City Cafe, Karen Karp, 3 minutes, V-1337 (Box 7)
  - Food Bank: NOAH GAFC Slide Set, V-1321 (Box 7)
  - FRAC Geraldine Henchy, Feb 25, 1992; V-1308 (Box 7)
  - General Mills, Food Banking Part I & II, V-1304 (Box 7)
  - God Bless the Child/ Nightline, Homeless (Covenant House), V-1322 (Box 7)
  - Gravani- Food Safety #2, V-1311 (Box 7)
  - Gravani- Food Safety (1:08) Spring 1991, Mar 12, 1991; V-1323 (Box 7)
  - Hameline, Dr. Thomas- H.E.L.P., Mar 12, 1996; V-1339 (Box 7)
  - Homeless in America: A Photographic Project (13 mins.), V-1334 (Box 7)
  - House Raising Walk (88) "The Excitement is Building," Habitat for Humanity, V-1331 (Box 7)
  - Life Inside Out, V-1300 (Box 7)
  - Joy in Our Town, Trinity Broadcasting Network (TBN), Aug 14, 2003; V-1333 (Box 7)
  - Karp, Karen- One City Cafe, Apr 25, 1996; V-1313 (Box 7)
  - Locked out of the American Dream, 50 mins, V-1338 (Box 7)
  - Marriott's Pathways Program, CBS Sunday Morning (10 mins), Jan, 1997; V-1327 (Box 7)
  - Mckeown, Sadie- CRA, Nov 5, 1991; V-1320 (Box 7)
  - Night Line Homeless, Sept 29, 1987; V-1329 (Box 7)
  - "Promises to Keep" Mitch Snyder, V-1317 (Box 7)
  - Rebuilding Neighborhoods- The Community Preservation Corporation, V-1324 (Box 7)
  - Rivera, Geraldo- Housing the Homeless with Mitch Snyder, Valerie Harper, John Voight, V-1330 (Box 7)
  - Runaways, MSNBC (5 mins), Feb, 2000; V-1332 (Box 7)
  - Shelter Boy (edited for 4th graders), V-1316 (Box 7)
  - Shelter Boy- Fox Broadcasting Comp. The Reporters, V-1328 (Box 7)
  - Shore, Bill- SOS, Apr 2, 1992; V-1305 (Box 7)
  - The Southern Tier Community Food Bank Student Project, 1989; V-1302, V-1325 (Box 7)
  - Southside, V-1335 (Box 7)
  - Southside Community Center- Roben Allong (HA 490 final project), V-1326 (Box 7)
  - St. Mary's Dining Room Winters- Quintet- George & Ilse, V-1307 (Box 7)
  - Stevenson, Paul- Community Development City of Ithaca, Feb 15, 1996; V-1318 (Box 7)
  - Student Presentation; 1. Homes 2. Homeless Education Program, Apr 23, 1991; V-1315 (Box 7)
  - Understanding Prepared Foods- Every 5th Child Program of the Chef and Child Foundation, Inc.- American Culinary Federation (13:17), V-1309 (Box 7)
  - With Hands & Hope (57:40), V-1310 (Box 7)
  - Hope for the Future: Educating Homeless Children and Youth Workshop, Mar 8, 1990; V-1346 (Box 8)
  - Housing and Feeding the Homeless: How the Hospitality Industry Can Make a Difference- H.E.C. 65 Ann Hales and James Eyster, Apr 21, 1990; V-1348 (Box 8)
  - Lisa Hack Acorn, Apr 18, 1991; V-1347 (Box 8)
  - On the Cutting Edge- Weingart Center (10 mins), V-1345 (Box 8)
  - Rewind: It Could Have Been Me, Lorie Loed, Morning Glory Films, Inc., V-1351 (Box 8)
  - Southside Shelter, V-1349 (Box 8)
  - Street Stories, 48 hours, V-1344 (Box 8)
  - WSTM- TV Homeless Program; Ann Hales, Cornell University, Nov 5, 1991; V-1350 (Box 8)